<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
  <content contentuid="hd475ea0bg823eg46e8g8cdeg4b02548dda26" version="1">Minthara's Journal</content>
  <content contentuid="hfceb1073gb022g4dc5g9ddagbf0a6e83f765" version="1">Its pages are filled with a neatly scribed log detailing hard days with militant precision. Towards the latter pages, the tone becomes uncertain and wavering. You see your name mentioned.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc315b2deg8855g498dgb4abg9dfb3eb2596a" version="1">13th, Eleasis - 1492&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have already grown weary of this hunt and we are but a few days set out. From the lavish delights of Menzoberranzan to these filthy backwater wilds, surrounded by contemptible goblins who aren't worth the air they breath. I don't know the exact nature of this 'Relic' that General Thorm has set me out to retrieve, but I hope it is worth the foul putrescence assaulting my olfaction.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;14th, Eleasis - 1492&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We've found an abandonded Temple to the contemptible moonwitch Selune. This should make a perfect base of operations while we scour the woods in search of the Relic. Our scouts, interestingly, came upon a small group of what seemed to be Tieflings and druids. They were driven back and not able to follow the druids to whichever mudpit hovel they are holed up in. I've ordered the search to be expanded to find these druids and remove the blight of their existance from my awareness&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;15th, Eleasis - 1492&lt;br&gt;Another Dream. I cant. It was. I felt as though there was something holding to my mind like the leash of a rabid Hyena. What a disturbing thought. I have never been more free than I am now, in service to the Absolute.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;16th, Eleasis - 1492&lt;br&gt;Goblins. These vile little towers of excrement will be my undoing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;17th, Eleasis - 1492&lt;br&gt;Again, my sleep troubles me. An ominous portent. I pray the Absolute strenghtens me for whatever lurks beyond the horizon of tomorrow&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;18th, Eleasis - 1492&lt;br&gt;No 'Relic'. No druids. No results. If we do not make progress soon, my earlier assertation and hyperbole about goblins being the death of me will be superseded by the real threat of General Thorms unbridled wrath&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;19th, Eleas&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Red. Blood. That...woman. Bodies. Corpses. Bodies. My dreams. I must sleep&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;20th, Eleasis - 1492&lt;br&gt;We had a scouting party go missing. When will this torment of filth end. I wish to slay my enemies that I might return to a replace with less reprehensible company. Though - perhaps in a twist of luck for both our mission and my Sanity - I just received word that another True Soul has just passed the checkpoint headed toward the Temple. Importantly, a True Soul that isn't a goblin. Maybe they'll be able to offer me some reprieve from my company and situation, and in doing so, offer the greater reprieve from my ailing mine and tempermant.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All glory to the Absolute.&lt;br&gt;</content>
</contentList>